Guide to the Cornell AIDS Action records,1987-1996.
Cornell AIDS Action records,1987-1996
- Series VI. Posters
  - United States
    - Missouri
      - Missouri Department of Health, "Stop Worrying About How You Won't Get AIDS. And Worry About How You Can." (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "This is the way many people deal with HIV." (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "Tres razones para no andar en la calle con los muchachos." (in Spanish) (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "Your Daughter Worries About AIDS." (Folder 6)
    - Montana
      - Montana AIDS/STD Program, "Get a Life" (Folder 6)
    - New Hampshire
      - New Hampshire Division of Public Health Services, "AIDS...Think about it." (Folder 6)
      - New Hampshire Division of Public Health Services, "HIV/AIDS: The Living Memorial" (Folder 6)
    - New Jersey
      - AIDS Coalition of Southern New Jersey, "We will be there..." (Folder 7)
      - New Jersey AIDS Hotline, "Cualquiera se puede infectar con el SIDA." (in Spanish) (Folder 7)
      - New Jersey AIDS Hotline, "Look at who can get AIDS." (Folder 7)
      - New Jersey Department of Health, "Does she or doesn't she?" (Folder 7)
      - New Jersey Department of Health, "Guess who else can get AIDS if you shoot drugs?", 1989 (Folder 7)
      - New Jersey Department of Health, "If you or your partner ever shot drugs...", 1989 (Folder 7)
      - New Jersey Department of Health, "She has her father's eyes and her mother's AIDS." (Folder 7)
      - New Jersey Department of Health, "SIDA Ataca Tamién a los Machos" (in Spanish) (Folder 7)
    - New Mexico
      - Albuquerque Area Indian Health Board, "Be Aware." (Folder 7)
      - Albuquerque Area Indian Health Board, "Be In Control." (Folder 7)
      - Albuquerque Area Indian Health Board, "Be Smart." (Folder 7)
      - Albuquerque Area Indian Health Board, "Be Strong." (Folder 7)
      - New Mexico Health and Environment Department, "AIDS: If You've Taken The Risks...Take The Test." [2 versions] (Folder 7)
      - Southwest AIDS Committee, "If You Love Them, Protect Them." (one copy in English, one copy in Spanish) (Folder 7)
    - New York
      - AIDS Drug Assistance Program, "I'm HIV positive..." (one copy in English, one copy in Spanish) (Folder 8)
      - AIDS Task Force of Central New York, "AIDS Walk + Run '93", 1993 (Folder 8)
      - AIDS Work, "The show all the signs of having HIV.", 1991 (Folder 8)
      - AIDS Work, "You Won't Get AIDS From A Public Pool." (Folder 8)
      - AIDS Work, "You Won't Get AIDS From Hide 'N' Seek." (Folder 8)
      - Alfred University, "Avoid The AIDS Ball" (Folder 8)
      - Alfred University, "Do you want to Screw Aids?" (Folder 8)
      - Alfred University, "Exposed" (Folder 8)
      - Alfred University, "he didn't use a condom" (Folder 8)
      - Alfred University, "One good reason to use condoms" (Folder 8)
      - Alfred University, "Who is HIV positive?" (Folder 8)
      - Cornell University, two heart-shaped collage posters (Folder 9)
      - Cornell University, "AIDS Means..." (Folder 9)
      - Cornell University, "Acquired Independent Determinant Style" (Folder 9)
      - Cornell University, "Chain Of Names" (Folder 9)
      - Cornell University, "Sex Sex Sex" (Folder 9)
      - Cornell University, "What AIDS Awareness Is..." (Folder 9)
      - Cornell University Health Center, "Numbers" (Folder 9)
      - Cornell University Health Center, "Respect Yourself" (Folder 9)
      - Cornell University, materials from World AIDS Day and the AIDS Memorial Quilt display at Cornell University. Items include: "The AIDS Memorial Quilt, WSH Memorial Room" poster, 2 hand-made posters for World Aids Day 1996, 4 posters of HIV/AIDS statistics and information, 1 "Fight AIDS" poster, an "AIDS Affects All" poster produced by the International Students and Scholars Office at Cornell (multilingual) and materials from the creation of the poster, a "Please Be Aware Some Posters Contain Nude Images" sign, a "Let's talk about love God's Way" paper, and papers containing comments from students and staff about the World AIDS Day poster display. Also AIDS memorial quilt 2000 materials and schedules and Names Quilt 1996 material. (Box 5, 7)
      - Hetrick-Martin Institute, "You are not alone!" (Folder 8)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "AIDS Dance-a-thon", 1992 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "AIDS Walk New York", 1993 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "A Rubber Is A Friend In Your Pocket", 1987 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "Circus for Life", 1992 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "Cojelo Con Cuidado...Take It Safely", 1989 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "If You Are HIV Positive:..." (one copy in English, one copy in Spanish), 1993 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "Music For Life: An AIDS Benefit Concert...", 1993 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "Once...Twice...Thrice...FIERCE!", 1991 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "Rubbers Are Bringing Men Together", 1992 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "Safer Sex: How To Do It", 1989 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "Safer Sex...Keep It Up!", 1991 (Folder 10)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, "Thank Goodness for Latex", 1989 (Folder 10)
      - New York State Division of Human Rights, "AIDS Discrimination Is Illegal" (Folder 8)
      - New York State Health Department, "Age won't protect you from AIDS" (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "Becoming A Father?" [2 versions] (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "Choices for Women" (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "Don't Die of Embarrassment" [2 versions], 1987 (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "El futuro está en tus manos." (in Spanish) (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "El SIDA no discrimina." (in Spanish) (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "Everybody's not doin' it." (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "Hablemos Entre Hombres" (in Spanish) (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "Our People Will Overcome AIDS Too" (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "Papi, ponte el sombrero." (in Spanish) (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "Proteja a su Familia Del SIDA" (in Spanish) (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "Put on your thinking cap." (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "¿Quién cuidará de tus seres queridos si tú faltas?" (in Spanish) (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "Simply having one on hand won't do any good." (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "To conquer fear is the beginning of wisdom." (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "¿Va a tener un bebe?" [one version in Spanish, another version with a different picture in English] (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "When you give the gift of love, make sure it's wrapped properly.", 1993 (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "You need a roll-on with maximum protection.", 1993 (Folder 11)
      - New York State Health Department, "You've got to be putting me on." (Folder 11)
      - Southern Tier AIDS Program (STAP), "be safe, be smart, be tested" [2 copies] (Folder 8)
      - Southern Tier AIDS Program (STAP), "With Unity And Pride...", 1995 (Folder 8)
      - SUNY Purchase, "See Dick. Dick Has AIDS." (Folder 8)
      - SUNY Purchase, "Uncle Alcoholic Fascist..." (Folder 8)
      - SUNY Purchase, "Whatever you call it, use it, or call it a night!" (Folder 8)
    - North Carolina
      - The Body Shop, "aids: how does aids impact your life?", 1993 (Folder 7)
    - Oklahoma
      - Oklahoma City Area HIV/AIDS Coalition, "AIDS: It's Everyones Problem" (Folder 7)
      - Oklahoma City Area HIV/AIDS Coalition, "AIDS: It's hard to avoid what you don't understand" (Folder 7)
      - Oklahoma City Area HIV/AIDS Coalition, "AIDS: Know The Facts" (Folder 7)
      - Oklahoma City Area HIV/AIDS Coalition, "AIDS: Teaching AIDS/Awareness Through Education" (Folder 7)
      - Oklahoma City Area HIV/AIDS Coalition, "Teaching AIDS Awareness Through Education" (Folder 7)
      - Oklahoma State Department of Health, "Be Safe. Use A Life Preserver." (Folder 7)
      - Oklahoma State Department of Health, "Date But Wait" (Folder 7)
      - Oklahoma State Department of Health, "Hey...Do You Know That You Can't Get AIDS From?" (Folder 7)
      - Oklahoma State Department of Health, "HIV: Will The Next STD You Get Be HIV?" (Folder 7)
      - Oklahoma State Department of Health, "No Time Bombs for your Baby" (Folder 7)
      - Oklahoma State Department of Health, "Shhhh! The greatest risk of AIDS spreading to Native Americans isn't from sex, IV drugs or alcohol abuse. It's from silence." (Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania, 1992
      - The Galaei Project, "SexoLatex" (Folder 7)
    - Tennessee
      - Tennessee Department of Health and Environment, "Don't just worry about HIV. Do something about it.", 1990 (Folder 12)
      - Tennessee Department of Health and Environment, "Do You Talk About AIDS On The First Date?" (Folder 12)
      - Tennessee Department of Health and Environment, "How Would You Deal With It If One Of You Got AIDS?" (Folder 12)
    - Texas
      - HEALTH EDCO, "Abstinence... It's Okay Not To Have Sex." (Folder 12)
      - HEALTH EDCO, "Aids Kills... Don't Drop Out Of Life." (Folder 12)
      - HEALTH EDCO, "STD... Don't Pass It On!" (Folder 12)
      - Texas A & M University, "Aggies and AIDS... A Tradition We Don't Need!" (Folder 12)
      - Texas Department of Health, "You Can Get AIDS From... (Folder 12)
    - Vermont
      - State Department of Health, "Don't forget your rubbers." (Folder 12)
      - State Department of Health, "Working Is Not Hazardous To Your Health.", 1989 (Folder 12)
    - Virginia
      - Virginia Department of Health, "If You Don't Like The Idea Of Safer Sex, May We Suggest An Alternative?" (Folder 12)
      - Virginia Department of Health, "Are You In The Dark?" (Folder 12)
      - Virginia Department of Health, "Infection Control" (Folder 12)
      - Virginia Department of Health, "Notice of 'Deemed Consent' For HIV Testing" (Folder 12)
      - Virginia Department of Health, "She has her father's eyes and her mother's AIDS." (Folder 12)
    - Washington
      - Seattle Indian Health Board, "Get With The Program!" (Folder 12)
      - Seattle Indian Health Board, "Let's Get Our Kids Hooked On Something... Before Someone Else Does." (Folder 12)
      - University of Washington School of Social Work, "Afterward, I worry about what I've done" (Folder 12)
      - University of Washington School of Social Work, "I Know What I Do Is Risky." (Folder 12)
    - Washington, D.C.
      - American Association for World Health, "A Community Commitment... World AIDS Day", 1992 (Folder 12)
      - American Association for World Health, "Shared Rights, Shared Responsibilities", 1995 (Folder 12)
      - American Association for World Health, "World Aids Day... One World One Hope", 1996 (Folder 12)
      - The Names Project, "The Names Project AIDS Memorial Quilt.", 1996 (Folder 12)
      - Whitman-Walker Clinic, "Men of the 90's do the safe thing." (Folder 12)
      - Whitman-Walker Clinic, "Positive, Negative, Both, Do The Safe Thing" (Folder 12)
      - Whitman-Walker Clinic, "Top, Bottom, Both, Do The Safe Thing" (Folder 12)
    - Wisconsin
      - Madison Advertising Federation, "Do You Know Who's Been Sleeping in Your Bed?" (Folder 12)
      - Madison Advertising Federation, "He Loves Me. He Loves Me Not." (Folder 12)
      - Wisconsin Department of Health and Social Services, "AIDS... Are YOU at Risk?" (Folder 12)
      - Wisconsin Department of Health and Social Services, "Don't Be A Casualty Of Casual Sex." (Folder 12)
      - Wisconsin Department of Health and Social Services, "Think About It." (Folder 12)
    - No Location
      - Academy for Educational Development, "Partners For A World Without AIDS" (Folder 13)
      - American Academy of Dermatology, "In 1985, I found out I was HIV positive..." (Folder 13)
      - American Social Health Association, "In Your Heart You Know It's Right", 1996 (Folder 13)
      - The Bacchus and Gamma Peer Education Network (Folder 13)
      - Design Industries Foundation Fights AIDS (DIFFA), "Safer Sex Is Hot Sex" [4 versions, all with Spanish and English] (Folder 13)
      - Institut Mérieux, no words (Folder 13)
      - Lifejackets Productions, "I [heart] Carefully", 1993 (Folder 13)
      - Lifejackets Productions, "Make Every Day World AIDS Day!", 1993 (Folder 13)
      - Lifejackets Productions, "What Are You Doing In The War Against AIDS?" [2 copies], 1994 (Folder 13)
      - The Names Project, "The Names Project- A National AIDS Memorial" (Folder 13)
      - National Council on Alcoholism and Drug Dependence, "Don't let drinking take your power away." (Folder 13)
      - National Council on Alcoholism and Drug Dependence, "If You Ever Shot Drugs Get Tested Before You Get Pregnant." (Folder 13)
      - National Council on Alcoholism and Drug Dependence, "Most babies with AIDS are born to mothers or fathers who have shot drugs." (Folder 13)
      - National Institute on Drug Abuse, "This Fatal Accident Was Caused By Teenagers Getting Stoned And Going Too Fast." (Folder 13)
      - Turtledove Clemens, Inc., "My Boyfriend Gave Me AIDS.", 1988 (Folder 13)
      - US Department of Health and Human Services Social Security Administration, "Lifeline... Benefits from Social Security" (Folder 13)
      - No distributor, "Do our children know..." (Folder 13)
      - No distributor, "Teach our children well- warn them about AIDS." (Folder 13)
  - International
    - Canada
      - AIDS Committee of Toronto, "Be Safe, Be Sure" (multi-lingual) (Folder 14)
      - AIDS Committee of Toronto, "By Talking To Each Other..." (Folder 14)
      - AIDS Committee of Toronto, "Love is a serious thing. Use condoms." (Folder 14)
      - AIDS Committee of Toronto, "Nobody does it better...or safer" (Folder 14)
      - AIDS Committee of Toronto, "Safer Sex Generation" (Folder 14)
      - AIDS Committee of Toronto, "Summer in the City" (Folder 14)
      - AIDS Committee of Toronto, "The Woman With Aids..." (Folder 14)
      - Black Coalition for AIDS Prevention and the Black Gay and Lesbian AIDS Discussion, "Somebody Else in your Picture?" (Folder 14)
    - Caribbean
      - Caribbean Epidemiology Centre (CAREC), "Unite Against AIDS" (Folder 14)
    - China
      - 7 different posters in Chinese, one with the English words "It's Natural" (Folder 14)
    - Japan
      - One poster in Japanese (Folder 14)
    - Nairobi
      - MAP International, "AIDS: a call beyond compassion" (Folder 14)
      - MAP International, "Ukimwi: jikinge na umkinge mwenzio..." (Folder 14)
    - Norway
      - Helsedirektoratet, "Are you properly dressed for the occasion?" (one copy in English, one copy in Norwegian) (Folder 14)
      - Helsedirektoratet, "Hvordan AIDS ikke smitter...", 1992 (Folder 14)
      - Helsedirektoratet, "Si Det Først!" (Folder 14)
      - Helsedirektoratet, "Ta det med ro i utlandet!" (Folder 14)
      - Helsedirektoratet, "Tenk deg om før du kaster deg uti det!" [2 versions] (Folder 14)
      - Helsedirektoratet, "Tror Du At P-Piller Beskytter Mot HIV Og Andre Sykdommer Som Smitter Seksuelt?" (Folder 14)
      - Landsforeningen Mot AIDS, "AIDS- En Global Trussel, Et Lokalt Ansvar", 1992 (Folder 14)
    - Puerto Rico
      - Departamento de Salud, "Yo Quiero Un Mundo Lleno De Vido Sin VIH/SIDA" (Folder 14)
    - Switzerland
      - World Health Organization, "Families Take Care" (Folder 14)
      - World Health Organization, "Shared Rights, Shared Responsibilities", 1995 (Folder 14)
      - World Health Organization, "Time To Act", 1993 (Folder 14)
    - Uganda
      - JSI Programme, six 2-month calendar posters covering the year 1993, with sayings in English and (Swahili?) (Folder 14)
      - JSI Programme, "Protect Yourself From Sexually Transmitted Diseases Use A Condom" (in English and (Swahili?)) (Folder 14)
      - JSI Programme Family Planning Private Sector, "AIDS Kills Use Condoms" (in English and (Swahili?)) (Folder 14)
  - Artwork
    - "AIDS Knows No Boundaries" (Folder 16)
  - Various posters about safe sex, HIV/AIDS (Box 6)